wrist_and_hand_oian_quiz = [
    {"question": "What is the origin of Flexor Carpi Radialis?", "options": ["Medial epicondyle of humerus", "Lateral epicondyle of humerus", "Distal half of anterior humerus"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Flexor Carpi Radialis?", "options": ["Radial styloid process", "Bases of second and third metacarpal bones", "Radial tuberosity"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Flexor Carpi Radialis?", "options": ["Extends hand at wrist", "Pronates forearm", "Flexes and abducts hand at wrist"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Flexor Carpi Radialis?", "options": ["Median nerve", "Ulnar nerve", "Radial nerve"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Extensor Carpi Ulnaris?", "options": ["Distal half of anterior humerus", "Lateral epicondyle of humerus", "Medial epicondyle of humerus"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Extensor Carpi Ulnaris?", "options": ["Base of the fifth metacarpal", "Base of the second metacarpal", "Radial styloid process"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Extensor Carpi Ulnaris?", "options": ["Extends and adducts hand at wrist", "Flexes and abducts hand at wrist", "Pronates forearm"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Extensor Carpi Ulnaris?", "options": ["Median nerve", "Ulnar nerve", "Radial nerve"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Flexor Digitorum Superficialis?", "options": ["Medial epicondyle of humerus", "Lateral epicondyle of humerus", "Distal half of anterior humerus"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Flexor Digitorum Superficialis?", "options": ["Middle phalanges of fingers 2-5", "Base of the fifth metacarpal", "Radial tuberosity"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Flexor Digitorum Superficialis?", "options": ["Extends fingers 2-5", "Abducts hand at wrist", "Flexes middle phalanges of fingers 2-5"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Flexor Digitorum Superficialis?", "options": ["Median nerve", "Ulnar nerve", "Radial nerve"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Extensor Digitorum?", "options": ["Lateral epicondyle of humerus", "Medial epicondyle of humerus", "Distal half of anterior humerus"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Extensor Digitorum?", "options": ["Distal phalanges of fingers 2-5", "Base of the second metacarpal", "Radial tuberosity"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Extensor Digitorum?", "options": ["Extends fingers 2-5", "Flexes middle phalanges of fingers 2-5", "Abducts hand at wrist"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Extensor Digitorum?", "options": ["Radial nerve", "Median nerve", "Ulnar nerve"], "answer": "a"}
]
